Jonathan Morrissey

22 The Drive, Mullen Park, Maynooth, Co. Kildare

jonathan.morrisseyto@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-morrissey/ https://github.com/Supersheep50

Mobile Number: 083 094 4671

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Principal Technical Recruiter with 7 years of experience hiring across all facets of the software development space. I have specialised in areas such as Product Management and Staff Engineering. Through this I have discovered a passion for software development that has led me to take several coding courses, including a diploma. I am excited for this next step in my career!

KEY SKILLS

- **Applications:** Microsoft Office Suite (Teams, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Access), G-Suite (Google docs, Gmail, Sheets, Slides, Drive), Lever, Greenhouse, Workday, Github, Gitpod, Atom, Slack, Zoom
- **Programming Languages:** CSS, HTML5, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React, Sinatra, Django
- Operating Systems: Windows, Mac OS, Linux
- Database Systems: SQLSecurity: Norton, McAfee
- Customer Service Experience: 10+ years in public facing roles
- Reception and Administration Skills: 7+ years in fast paced tech office environments.
- Languages: English

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2022 - Present	Code Institute, Blackrock, Dublin, Ireland.
	Full Stack Software Development Diploma

Modules: HTML, CSS, Python, Javascript, React, SQL, APIS &

Frameworks, Testing Code, Design Thinking

2019 Lighthouse Labs, Toronto, Ontario, Canada.

Certificate in Computer Programming

Modules: HTML, CSS, Github, Ruby, Sinatra

2008-2012 University of Limerick, Limerick, Ireland.

Bachelor of Arts in English & History

Second Class Honours Degree

Modules: English literature, European History, American History

2001 – 2007 Crescent College Comprehensive, Limerick, Ireland.

Leaving Certificate

WORK EXPERIENCE 06/2021 - Present

Stripe, Dublin, Ireland Principal Technical Recruiter

- Lead PM Hiring for all of EMEA
- Partner with EMEA Product leadership to build out PM processes
- Sourcing, interviewing and handling all facets of PM Recruitment
- Partner with colleagues in AMER and APAC to build out consistent PM Recruitment Infrastructure
- Mentor 1 Recruiter and 1 Researcher on the PM Recruitment Team

11/2020 - 06/2021

Q4, Toronto, Canada Lead Technical Recruiter

- Lead RnD hiring for the business
- Mentor and guide more junior members of the team
- Major focus on building out new processes
- Help to push forward Employer Branding
- Work with RnD and Talent leaders to build out Hiring Roadmap

10/2017 - 11/2020

Shopify, Ottawa, Canada Senior Technical Recruiter

- · Handle all facets of recruitment within RnD
- Help plan and design annual hiring strategies for several product lines
- Work with the business leadership to design high-impact teams
- Conduct daily, weekly, and monthly meetings with key stakeholders on the product line
- Liaise with external staffing agencies to assist in headcount targets
- Provide guidance to hiring managers on best interview practices
- Project coordination hiring strategies, off-sites, events

12/2015 - 10/2017

Randstad, Toronto, Canada Recruitment Advisor

- Find and develop new clients within the technologies space
- Ensure the long term success of the client
- Provide advice to clients on their recruitment challenges
- Gather and prepare RFP for potential business

INTERESTS

- I am obsessed with tech and the digital space in general. Coding has become a main hobby of mine and I try to stay on top of current trends. I spend a lot of time on YouTube.
- Video Games: I am an avid and passionate video gamer! I host a video game podcast with 2 of my friends: <u>Hey Look Listen!</u>

• Reading & Writing: I always have a new book on the go and have even tried writing my own novel in the past.

REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST